Guide to the Richard S. Buswell, Photographs of Abandoned Wooden Buildings and Artifacts in Montana
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Photographs of Abandoned Wooden Buildings and Artifacts in Montana
1986-2017
WA Photos 410
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
2.1
5 boxes
Photographs created by Richard S. Buswell of Helena, Montana, of abandoned wooden buildings and artifacts in Montana, 1975-2016, and printed by him, 1986-2017. Images include exteriors and interiors of cabins, barns, hotels, general stores, and blacksmith shops, as well as railroad trestles and cemeteries.
Buswell, Richard S., 1945-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Richard S. Buswell on the Arthur Corbitt Hoskins Memorial Fund, 2007-2015.
Purchased from Richard S. Buswell on the Frederick W. and Carrie S. Beinecke Fund for Western Americana, 2013-2017.
Gift of Richard S. Buswell, 2016.
Arrangement
Organized chronologically under headings for years between 1975 and 2016 by date of image capture with the printing date reflected in the date column and then alphabetically under each heading.
Richard S. Buswell (born 1945)
Richard S. Buswell is a medical doctor and photographer living in Helena, Montana. He published his first photographic work in the student newspaper of Helena High School in 1963. He continued his education at Carroll College from 1963 to 1966 and earned his medical degree from Oregon Health & Science University in 1970. The following year he began photographing abandoned towns, mining camps, and homesteads across Montana. In 1997 the University of Montana published his first book, Echoes: A Visual Reflection. Since then Buswell has published five more books including Close to Home: Photographs (New Mexico, 2013) and What They Left Behind: Photographs (New Mexico, 2017). In addition to the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library, his images are held by the Smithsonian American Art Museum, the National Gallery of Art (material formerly held by the Corcoran Gallery of Art), and the George Eastman House.
Scope and Contents
Photographs created by Richard Buswell of Helena, Montana, of abandoned wooden buildings and artifacts in Montana, 1975-2015, and printed by him, 1986-2016. Images include exteriors and interiors of cabins, barns, hotels, general stores, and blacksmith shops, as well as railroad trestles and cemeteries. Artifacts include examples of bedsprings, bird cages, blacksmith and carpentry tools, bottles, chairs, gardening implements, hand carts, hay rakes, mill stamps, pianos, toys, and wood stoves, as well as animal bones and skulls.
Abandoned buildings -- Montana -- Pictorial works; Montana -- Pictorial works; Photographic prints; Photographs; Antiquities -- Montana -- Pictorial works; Richard S. Buswell, LLC
- Photographs, 1986–2017
  Scope and Contents
  Photographs created by Richard Buswell of Helena, Montana, of abandoned wooden buildings and artifacts in Montana, 1975-2016, and printed as selenium-toned gelatin silver prints by him, 1986-2017.
  Arrangement
  Organized chronologically under headings for years between 1975 and 2016 by date of image capture with the printing date reflected in the date column and then alphabetically under each heading.
  - 1975
    - Wagon and Grindstone, Summer 1975, 1993 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1976
    - Railroad Trestle, Summer 1976, 2001 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1977
    - Hayloft No. 1, Summer 1977, 1999 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1978
    - Loading Ramp and Mine Dump, Summer 1978, 1991 January 12 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1979
    - Aspen Covered Cabin, Summer 1979, 1990 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Aspen in a Cabin, Summer 1979, 1993 January 10 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Aspen in a Cabin Door, Summer 1979, 2001 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Bannack, Summer 1979, 1990 March 12 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Hand Cart, Summer 1979, 1990 March 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1980
    - Bedframe in Snowstorm, Late Winter 1980, 2008 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Dangling Wall, Summer 1980, 2007 January 28 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Head Frame, Summer 1980, 1990 February 8 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Mill Stamps, Summer 1980, 2001 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Snow-Bound, Late Winter 1980, 1994 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - 1981
    - Cemetery, Summer 1981, 1989 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Cupboard, Summer 1981, 1989 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Gold Mill No. 4, Summer 1981, 1989 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Windows, Summer 1981, 1989 April 9 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - 1982
    - Bay Window, Summer 1982, 1989 February 4 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Charcoal Ovens No. 1, Summer 1982, 2001 March 17 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Charcoal Ovens No. 2, Summer 1982, 2000 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Gold Mill No. 2, Summer 1982, 2001 February 1 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Hay Rakes, Late Winter 1982, 1989 January 26 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Lime Kiln, Summer 1982, 1989 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Newspaper Insulation, Summer 1982, 1993 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Soddy, Summer 1982, 1999 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Staircase, Summer 1982, 1989 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - 1983
    - Bedframe Gate, Summer 1983, 2001 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Bunk House, Summer 1983, 1988 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Burlap in a Window, Summer 1983, 1988 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Eroded Mill Tailings No. 1, Summer 1983, 1994 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - General Store, Summer 1983, 2004 February 28 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Gold Mill No. 1, Summer 1983, 1993 January 16 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Homestead No. 1, Summer 1983, 1988 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Icehouse, Summer 1983, 2002 January 2 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Loading Chute, Summer 1983, 2000 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Mine Track, Summer 1983, 2000 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Pigeon on a Homestead, Summer 1983, 1988 January 9 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - 1984
    - Coke Ovens No. 3, Summer 1984, 1987 February 7 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Lakeshore Town No. 2, Summer 1984, 1987 January 22 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Pantry, Fall 1984, 1994 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Prairie Church, Summer 1984, 1987 January 4 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Screen Door, Fall 1984, 1987 February 22 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - 1985
    - Bellows and Leaves, Summer 1985, 1986 February 17 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Hotel in Winter, Winter 1985, 1992 April 5 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Pump Organ Keys, Summer 1985, 2004 February 29 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - Snow Blanket, Early Spring 1985, 20008 March 29 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - Stacked Wagon Wheels, 1985, 1998 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - Winter Grave, Winter 1985, 2001 January 25 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - 1986
    - Boat Dock, Summer 1986, 1987 January 4 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - Feeding Trough No. 1, Summer 1986, 1996 December 29 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - Feeding Trough No. 2, Summer 1986, 1992 April 4 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - Mine Bench, Summer 1986, 2001 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - Ore Chutes, Summer 1986, 1986 December 28 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Straw Mattress, Summer 1986, 1986 December 20 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - 1988
    - Blacksmith's Bench, Summer 1988, 1991 February 21 (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - Moss-Covered Mine Dump, Summer 1988, 1992 March 9 (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - Sunlit Mill Rafters, Summer 1988, 1988 March 8 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - 1989
    - Gold Mill No. 3, Summer 1989, 1990 January 18 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - 1990
    - Suspended Ladder, Summer 1990, 1994 February 14 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - 1991
    - Cupolas, Summer 1991, 2000 February 20 (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - Ventilation Shaft, Summer 1991, 1998 March 11 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - Wood Stove, Summer 1991, 1998 March 16 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - 1992
    - Mill Cam Shaft No. 1, Summer 1992, 1992 December 24 (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - Mill Cam Shaft No. 2, Summer 1992, 1994 March 6 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - To the Cellar, Summer 1992, 1992 December 21 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - 1993
    - Great Northern Tunnel No. 1, Late Winter 1993, 1994 January 24 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Great Northern Tunnel No. 2, Late Winter 1993, 1994 January 29 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - Medicine Lodge, Summer 1993, 2006 February 26 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - 1994
    - Brickyard Vents, Early Winter 1994, 1999 February 15 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - Hoe in a Lime Bin, Summer 1994, 1995 January 30 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Mill Gear, Summer 1994, 2002 March 17 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - Sod Roof, Summer 1994, 2006 February 12 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - 1995
    - Beneath a Window, Summer 1995, 1995 December 16 (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - Cellar Door, Summer 1995, 1995 December 18 (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - Chicken Coop Sentinels, Summer 1995, 1995 December 23 (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Potato Cellar, Summer 1995, 1996 January 21 (Box 1, Folder 77)
    - Stove Top, Summer 1985, 1996 January 15 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - 1996
    - Horse Shed, Summer 1996, 1996 December 23 (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Mill Footing, Summer 1996, 1996 December 14 (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Silo, Summer 1996, 2004 February 22 (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Three Ladies: Newspaper-Wallpaper, Summer 1996, 1998 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - To the Loft, Summer 1996, 1996 December 14 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - 1997
    - Chair, Summer 1997, 2005 January 29 (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - Dredge Interior, Summer 1997, 1998 February 2 (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Mill Boiler, Interior, Summer 1997, 1998 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Mine Tunnel, Summer 1997, 1998 January 29 (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Newspaper in a Window, Summer 1997, 2002 February 12 (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Print Shop, Summer 1997, 2008 March 30 (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Smelter Slag, Summer 1997, 1998 January 17 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - 1998
    - Bedsprings, Summer 1998, 2002 March 10 (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Bottles in a Brewery, Summer 1998, 2008 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Buggy Seat, Summer 1998, 2003 February 8 (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Glue Pot, Summer 1998, 2003 February 2 (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Mannequin Head, Summer 1998, 1999 January 3 (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - Mine Pipes, Summer 1998, 1999 February 20 (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - Piano Hammers, Summer 1998, 2005 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - Quarry Mast, Summer 1998, 1999 February 8 (Box 2, Folder 98)
      Gift of Richard S. Buswell, 2016
    - Spring House, Summer 1998, 2002 March 10 (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - Three Mannequin Heads, Summer 1998, 2008 February 8 (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Tram Wheels, Summer 1998, 2010 February 13 (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - Typewriter, Summer 1998, 2003 February 1 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - 1999
    - Bird Cage, Summer 1999, 2000 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - Boudoir, Summer 1999, 2002 March 11 (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - Cabin Interior, Summer 1999, 2002 February 24 (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Chimney, Summer 1999, 1999 December 20 (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - Dredge Pump, Summer 1999, 2005 February 5 (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - Mill Window, Summer 1999, 2000 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - Shelf, Summer 1999, 2002 March 4 (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - Wall Drawing, Summer 1999, 2000 January 9 (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - Water Wheel, Summer 1999, 2000 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 111)
  - 2000
    - Bar Panel, Summer 2000, 2001 January 11 (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - Blackboard (Juniors 1910), Summer 2000, 2003 February 8 (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - Blacksmith's Tools, Summer 2000, 2001 January 8 (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - Blacksmith's Window, Summer 2000, 2003 February 2 (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - Boiler Tubes, Fall 2000, 2002 February 16 (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - Bone Wagon, Summer 2000, 2003 February 9 (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - Burlap Drapes, Summer 2000, 2001 January 21 (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - Ceiling, Summer 2000, 2000 December 10 (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - Mossy Shingles, Summer 2000, 2001 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - Rafters, Summer 2000, 2002 March 4 (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - Steam Radiator, Summer 2000, 2008 March 23 (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - Stone Chimney, Summer 2000, 2000 December 20 (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - Stuffed Chair, Summer 2000, 2000 December 31 (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - Where Swallows Lived, Summer 2000, 2002 February 24 (Box 2, Folder 125)
  - 2001
    - Cards, Summer 2001, 2002 January 6 (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - Carriage Seats, Summer 2001, 2006 February 13 (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Chair Back, Summer 2001, 2010 December 30 (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - Chinese Lanterns, Summer 2001, 2002 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - Coffee Pots, Summer 2001, 2004 March 6 (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - Feeding Trough No. 3, Summer 2001, 2002 January 26 (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - Hay Feeder, Summer 2001, 2002 January 14 (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - Homestead Ceiling, Summer 2001, 2002 January 6 (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - Knots, Summer 2001, 2004 February 28 (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - Lean-To, Summer 2001, 2003 February 1 (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - Once a Windmill, Summer 2001, 2002 January 27 (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - Player Piano Drum, Summer 2001, 2005 January 30 (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - Two Knots, Summer 2001, 2011 February 27 (Box 2, Folder 138)
  - 2002
    - Bedroom, Summer 2002, 2003 January 20 (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - Carousel Hooves, Summer 2002, 2005 February 5 (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - Fraternal Hall, Summer 2002, 2003 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - Hay Grapple, Summer 2002, 2003 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - Horse Collars, Summer 2002, 2003 March 22 (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - Trunk Lid, Summer 2002, 2003 January 26 (Box 2, Folder 144)
  - 2003
    - Barn Loft, Summer 2003, 2004 January 18 (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - Cactus-Covered Roof No.1, Summer 2003, 2004 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - Charcoal Oven, Interior, Summer 2003, 2004 February 2 (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - Combine Belt, Summer 2003, 2004 January 17 (Box 2, Folder 148)
    - Honey Comb, Summer 2003, 2004 February 7 (Box 2, Folder 149)
    - Models, Summer 2003, 2004 February 7 (Box 2, Folder 150)
    - Saddle Blanket, Summer 2003, 2004 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 151)
    - Sheep Shed, Interior, Summer 2003, 2004 February 13 (Box 2, Folder 152)
    - Tin Ceiling, Summer 2003, 2004 January 25 (Box 2, Folder 153)
    - Wicker Basket, Summer 2003, 2004 January 24 (Box 2, Folder 154)
  - 2004
    - Bull's Eye, Summer 2004, 2005 January 15 (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - Cast Iron Stove, Summer 2004, 2005 January 2 (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - Chicken Roost, Summer 2004, 2005 January 9 (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - Chimney Cap, Summer 2004, 2005 January 23 (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - Desk Slots, Summer 2004, 2008 March 22 (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - Half House, Summer 2004, 2005 January 1 (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - Linoleum, Summer 2004, 2008 March 9 (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - Porch, Summer 2004, 2004 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - Sickle, Summer 2004, 2005 January 1 (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - Telephone, Summer 2004, 2005 January 8 (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - Thresher Blades, Summer 2004, 2005 January 15 (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - Victrola Louvers, Summer 2004, 2005 January 2 (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - White Gate, Summer 2004, 2005 January 22 (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - 2005
    - Barn Loft Basketball, Summer 2005, 2006 February 4 (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - Barn Siding, Summer 2005, 2012 March 4 (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - Box Interior, Summer 2005, 2008 March 8 (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - Cash Register, Summer 2005, 2008 March 9 (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - Clothes Wringer, Summer 2005, 2006 January 23 (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - Coffee Can, Summer 2005, 2006 January 16 (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - Decorative Stove, Summer 2005, 2006 January 22 (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - Decorative Stove No. 1, Summer 2005, 2006 January 16 (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - Fractured Window, Summer 2005, 2006 January 28 (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - Pine Cone, Summer 2005, 2006 February 27 (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - Pipe Fittings, Summer 2005, 2006 January 8 (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - Plow Seat No. 1, Summer 2005, 2006 January 22 (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - Plow Seat No. 2, Summer 2005, 2006 January 23 (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - Sheep Herder's Cabin, Summer 2005, 2006 January 29 (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - Swallows' Nests, Summer 2005, 2006 January 29 (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - Teepee Burner, Summer 2005, 2006 February 5 (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - Telephone Insulators, Summer 2005, 2006 January 9 (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - Wagon Top, Summer 2005, 2006 February 5 (Box 3, Folder 185)
  - 2006
    - Dashboard Plate, Summer 2006, 2006 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - Elixirs, Summer 2006, 2007 January 14 (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - Farm Tool, Summer 2006, 2007 January 13 (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - Hoist Wheel, Summer 2006, 2007 January 6 (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - Hotel, Second Floor, Summer 2006, 2007 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - Rheostat - Side View, Fall 2006, 2007 January 6 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Rheostat - Top View, Fall 2006, 2007 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Rolled Newspapers, Summer 2006, 2007 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - Saddle, Summer 2006, 2007 January 7 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Three Milk Cans, Summer 2006, 2007 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - Tire, Summer 2006, 2006 December 31 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - Window Shade, Summer 2006, 2007 January 7 (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - 2007
    - Barn Ventilator, Summer 2007, 2008 January 19 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Camp Stove, Summer 2007, 2008 February 3 (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - Chap Fringe, Summer 2007, 2008 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - Coffee Can Scene, Summer 2007, 2010 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - Cow Skull, Summer 2007, 2008 February 24 (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - Door Jamb, Summer 2007, 2008 February 2 (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - The Emperor's Family, Fall 2007, 2008 February 17 (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - Horn, Summer 2007, 2008 January 19 (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - Horse Collar Swing, Summer 2007, 2008 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - Pedals, Summer 2007, 2008 March 2 (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - Potato Bucket, Summer 2007, 2008 January 12 (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - Potato Shovel, Summer 2007, 2008 March 8 (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - Raptor Skeleton, Summer 2007, 2008 January 28 (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - Shell Casings, Summer 2007, 2008 January 20 (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - Scrap Iron, Summer 2007, 2008 March 2 (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - Shingle Warranty, Summer 2007, 2008 February 2 (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - Shoe Tree, Summer 2007, 2008 February 24 (Box 3, Folder 214)
    - Sickle Guards, Summer 2007, 2008 January 29 (Box 3, Folder 215)
    - Skull Sutures, Fall 2007, 2008 February 16 (Box 3, Folder 216)
    - Window Frame, Summer 2007, 2008 January 12 (Box 3, Folder 217)
  - 2008
    - Abacus, Summer 2008, 2009 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 218)
    - Fractured Window No. 2, Summer 2008, 2009 February 7 (Box 3, Folder 219)
    - Saline Seep No. 2, Summer 2008, 2009 January 18 (Box 3, Folder 220)
    - Seed Pods in a Corral, Summer 2008, 2012 March 3 (Box 3, Folder 221)
    - Teapot, Summer 2008, 2009 January 2 (Box 3, Folder 222)
  - 2009
    - Abandoned Garlic, Summer 2009, 2010 January 2 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Back Door, Summer 2009, 2010 January 1 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - Bone Series No. 1, Fall 2009, 2010 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Bone Series No. 2, Summer 2009, 2012 March 10 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Bone Series No. 3, Summer 2009, 2010 January 3 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Chinese Fan, Summer 2009, 2010 January 31 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Chinese Herbs, Summer 2009, 2010 January 31 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Dental Crowns, Summer 2009, 2010 January 30 (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Gas Lamp, Summer 2009, 2010 January 23 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Ore Chute, Summer 2009, 2010 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - Two Fence Posts, Summer 2009, 2012 March 3 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - Weaning Mask, Summer 2009, 2010 January 23 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - Wicker Chair, Summer 2009, 2010 January 9 (Box 4, Folder 235)
  - 2010
    - Coyote Skull, Summer 2010, 2011 February 19 (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - Horse Mandible, Summer 2010, 2011 January 23 (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - Indian Grave, Summer 2010, 2014 February 3 (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - Jail Curtains, Summer 2010, 2011 February 12 (Box 4, Folder 239)
    - Light Socket, Summer 2010, 2011 January 23 (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - Miner's Glove, Summer 2010, 2011 February 5 (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - Nostril Interior, Summer 2010, 2011 February 20 (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - Peeling Door, Summer 2010, 2011 February 19 (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - Pitcher, Summer 2010, 2011 February 13 (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - Skull Tree, Summer 2010, 2011 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - Stacked Lumber, Summer 2010, 2011 February 12 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - Wind Vanes, Summer 2010, 2011 February 20 (Box 4, Folder 247)
  - 2011
    - Beaver Skull, Summer 2011, 2012 January 14 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - Chinese Lantern Figure, Summer 2011, 2012 February 18 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Cow Pelvis, Summer 2011, 2012 February 5 (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - Crushed Radiator, Summer 2011, 2012 February 11 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - Decaying Skull, Summer 2011, 2012 January 14 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - Elk Teeth, Summer 2011, 2012 January 15 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Knobby Antler, Summer 2011, 2012 February 12 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Knot Pattern, Summer 2011, 2012 January 30 (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Lichen Covered Stairs, Summer 2011, 2012 February 4 (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Mill Ceiling, Summer 2011, 2012 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Mill Floor, Summer 2011, 2012 January 14 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - Moose Antlers, Summer 2011, 2012 February 26 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Ram's Horn, Summer 2011, 2012 January 28 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Ribs, Summer 2011, 2012 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - Sheet Metal, Summer 2011, 2012 February 5 (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Spindles, Summer 2011, 2012 February 19 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Spout, Summer 2011, 2012 January 21 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - Stacked Chairs, Summer 2011, 2012 January 21 (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - To the Garden, Summer 2011, 2012 February 4 (Box 4, Folder 266)
  - 2012
    - Bird Houses, Summer 2012, 2013 January 14 (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - Bulb Sockets, Summer 2012, 2013 January 17 (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Cardboard Siding, Summer 2012, 2013 January 12 (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Chinese Lantern No. 2, Summer 2012, 2013 January 31 (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Cross Cut Saws, Summer 2012, 2013 January 23 (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Doll Face, Summer 2012, 2013 January 12 (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Head Board, Summer 2012, 2013 January 27 (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Hoist Drum, Summer 2012, 2013 January 29 (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Mine Bits, Summer 2012, 2013 January 14 (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Player Piano Pins, Summer 2012, 2013 January 29 (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - Rattlesnake, Summer 2012, 2013 January 31 (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - Sole, Summer 2012, 2013 January 14 (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Tire No. 2, Summer 2012, 2013 January 8 (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Wheel Cleats, Summer 2012, 2013 January 9 (Box 4, Folder 280)
  - 2013
    - Assay Plate, Summer 2013, 2014 January 6 (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Broom, Summer 2013, 2014 January 28 (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Calf Spine, Summer 2013, 2013 December 28 (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - Church Window, Summer 2013, 2014 January 27 (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Cow Mandible, Summer 2013, 2014 January 24 (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - Doll Parts, Summer 2013, 2013 December 28 (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - Dried Fish, Summer 2013, 2014 January 2 (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - Electric Relays, Fall 2013, 2014 January 6 (Box 4, Folder 288)
    - Feathers, Summer 2013, 2013 December 31 (Box 4, Folder 289)
    - Hoist Cable, Summer 2013, 2014 January 20 (Box 4, Folder 290)
    - Mandible Exterior, Summer 2013, 2014 January 13 (Box 4, Folder 291)
    - Mandible Interior, Summer 2013, 2014 January 13 (Box 4, Folder 292)
    - On a Mine Dump, Fall 2013, 2014 January 18 (Box 4, Folder 293)